There you are.
ها أنت ذا.
What is your problem?
ما هي مشكلتك؟
Help.
مساعدة.
How rustic!
كيف ريفي!
Su Ziying.
سو زيينغ.
Su Ziying!
سو تسى يينغ!
Keep the music down!
حافظ على الموسيقى منخفضة!
Su Ziying,
سو تسي يينغ ،
please
من فضلك
be my girlfriend.
كوني حبيبتي.
You must be out of your mind.
يجب أن تكون وتا عقلك.
She's shy.
هي خجولة.
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
=EP6 The Bossy Guy's Invalid Love Confession=
= EP6 اعتراف الرجل المتسلط بالحب غير الصالح =
Oh.
أوه.
She doesn't like roses.
إنها لا تحب الورود.
Mm.
مم.
(Timetable)
(الجدول الزمني)
It's the girls' dorm. You mustn't come in without permission!
إنه مسكن البنات.  لا يجب أن تأتي بدون إذن!
Here we are.
نحن هنا.
Ye Juncheng's cutie,
يي جونتشنغ اللطيفة ،
please sign for the dolls.
الرجاء التوقيع على الدمى.
Is that you?
هل هذا أنت؟
Ye Juncheng's baby, please sign for it.
طفل يي جونتشنغ ، من فضلك وقع عليه.
Ye Juncheng's honey.
يي جونتشنغ العسل.
Who's Ye Juncheng's honey?
من هو عسل يي جونتشنغ؟
Please sign for it.
الرجاء التوقيع عليها.
I'll overrun.
سوف اجتاح.
Girl,
بنت،
are you the honey?
هل انت العسل
You know what?
أتعلم؟
It must be
يجب ان يكون
(The Neurotic Personality of Our Time) Ye Juncheng's first time to pursue a girl.
(الشخصية العصبية لعصرنا) أول مرة تلاحق فيها يي جونتشنغ فتاة.
What he did is really funny!
ما فعله هو مضحك حقا!
Him?
له؟
He won't be able to get Ziying.
لن يتمكن من الحصول على Ziying.
Unless...
إلا إذا...
He forces her.
يجبرها.
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
Hey, Ziying!
مرحبًا ، Ziying!
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Mr. Ye just wants a private talk with Miss Su.
السيد يي يريد فقط محادثة خاصة مع الآنسة سو.
After that, he'll let her go.
بعد ذلك ، سيسمح لها بالرحيل.
Su Ziying!
سو تسى يينغ!
Tell me what you want.
قل لي ماذا تريد.
Under what circumstances would you be my girlfriend?
تحت أي ظروف ستكون صديقتي؟
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
what is your problem?
ما هي مشكلتك؟
You didn't want the roses.
أنت لا تريد الورود.
You returned my gifts, too.
لقد أعدت هداياي أيضًا.
What I learned from TV series didn't work at all.
ما تعلمته من المسلسلات التلفزيونية لم ينجح على الإطلاق.
I don't want to waste time anymore.
لا أريد أن أضيع الوقت بعد الآن.
Tell me what you want.
قل لي ماذا تريد.
Anything.
اى شى.
Or...
أو...
Do you want
هل تريد
some cash?
بعض النقود؟
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
I'll never adore a stingy man like you.
لن أعشق أبدًا رجل بخيل مثلك.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
Just be my girlfriend.
فقط كوني صديقتي.
I'll give you
سأعطيك
anything you want.
اي شيء تريده.
Ye Juncheng, you're so full of yourself.
يي جونتشنغ ، أنت مليء بنفسك.
Su Ziying,
سو تسي يينغ ،
don't go too far.
لا تذهب بعيدا.
Ye Juncheng,
يي جونتشنغ ،
don't make me slap you.
لا تجعلني اصفعك.
Isn't it a classic dialogue of a bossy rich man?
أليس هو حوار كلاسيكي لرجل ثري متسلط؟
So dramatic.
درامي كثيرا.
Ye Juncheng. Open the door, Ye Juncheng!
يي جونتشنغ ، افتح الباب ، يي جونتشنغ!
Ye Juncheng, we can call the police.
يي جونتشنغ ، يمكننا الاتصال بالشرطة.
It's okay. It's okay.
حسنا.  حسنا.
You'd better let me go.
من الأفضل أن تدعني أذهب.
Or Lin Han would break in.
أو لين هان سيقتحم.
Break in?
يقتحم؟
Seriously?
بشكل جاد؟
Come on.
هيا.
Get out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
Three, two, one.
ثلاثة اثنان واحد.
Ah!
آه!
(Who wouldn't expect a sweet relationship in the university?)
(من منا لا يتوقع علاقة لطيفة في الجامعة؟)
Girl,
بنت،
are you the honey?
هل انت العسل
It's...
انها...
You.
أنت.
Ye Juncheng asked me to give all these things to you.
طلبت مني يي جونتشنغ أن أعطي كل هذه الأشياء لك.
Who's Ye Juncheng's sweetheart?
من هو حبيبة يي جونتشنغ؟
Sweetheart?
حبيبة القلب؟
Here I am.
ها أنا.
Mr. Miser,
السيد مصر ،
have you ever pursued a girl?
هل سبق لك أن تابعت فتاة؟
I haven't,
ليس لدي،
of course.
بالطبع.
Then stay at home
ثم ابق في المنزل
and let me do it.
واسمحوا لي أن أفعل ذلك.
You?
أنت؟
What are you going to do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)